A Guide to the Richmond Jaycees, 1936-2002
Library of Virginia
- Photographs, 1975-1997.
  - Beach Music Festival, not dated. (Box 135, Folder 2)
  - Beach Music Festival, not dated. (Box 135, Folder 3)
  - Beach Music Festival, not dated. (Box 135, Folder 4)
  - Beach Music Festival, not dated. (Box 135, Folder 5)
  - Beach Music Festival, not dated. (Box 135, Folder 6)
  - Beach Music Festival slides, 1984. (Box 135, Folder 7)
  - Board Retreat, 1991. (Box 135, Folder 8)
  - Dan Boswell, not dated. (Box 135, Folder 9)
  - Bowling, 1995. (Box 135, Folder 10)
  - Bowling for Fun, 1991. (Box 135, Folder 11)
  - Bus Party negatives, 1990. (Box 135, Folder 12)
  - Camp Virginia Jaycees, not dated. (Box 135, Folder 13)
  - Casino Night, not dated. (Box 135, Folder 14)
  - Chairman's Project Guide Training, not dated. (Box 135, Folder 15)
  - Childrens Festival, not dated. (Box 135, Folder 16)
  - Christmas Parade, 1990. (Box 135, Folder 17)
  - Christmas Parade, 1991. (Box 135, Folder 18)
  - Christmas Parade, not dated. (Box 135, Folder 19)
  - Christmas Parade, not dated. (Box 135, Folder 20)
  - Christmas Parade, not dated. (Box 135, Folder 21)
  - Christmas Parade Charity Ball, ca. 1987-1988. (Box 135, Folder 22)
  - Christmas Party, not dated. (Box 135, Folder 23)
  - Christmas Tree Sale, 1990. (Box 136, Folder 1)
  - Christmas Tree Sale, not dated. (Box 136, Folder 2)
  - Christmas Tree Sale negatives, not dated. (Box 136, Folder 3)
  - Stuart Cox, not dated. (Box 136, Folder 4)
  - Chief Custalow of the Mattaponi, 1990. (Box 136, Folder 5)
  - Frances Daniel, not dated. (Box 136, Folder 6)
  - Dinner Meeting, 1990. (Box 136, Folder 7)
  - Dinner Meeting, 1991. (Box 136, Folder 8)
  - Dinner Meeting, not dated. (Box 136, Folder 9)
  - Dribble and Shoot, 1986-1987. (Box 136, Folder 10)
  - Dribble and Shoot, 1991. (Box 136, Folder 11)
  - Dribble and Shoot, 1991. (Box 136, Folder 12)
  - Duck Race, not dated. (Box 136, Folder 13)
  - Family Picnic, 1990. (Box 136, Folder 14)
  - Fingerprinting Children, ca. 1989. (Box 136, Folder 15)
  - Firefighter Award Ceremony, not dated. (Box 136, Folder 16)
  - Firefighters Awards negatives, not dated. (Box 136, Folder 17)
  - Delegate Franklin P. Hall, not dated. (Box 136, Folder 18)
  - Frank Hall -- Model General Assembly, not dated. (Box 136, Folder 19)
  - Halloween Party, 1990. (Box 136, Folder 20)
  - Halloween Party, not dated. (Box 136, Folder 21)
  - Halloween Party for Big Brothers/Big Sisters, not dated. (Box 136, Folder 22)
  - Junior Chamber of Commerce 76th Annual Meeting -- Lexington, not dated. (Box 136, Folder 23)
  - Kat's Birthday Party, 1997. (Box 136, Folder 24)
  - Ed Lane Speaking at Dinner Meeting, ca. 1960. (Box 136, Folder 25)
  - Leadership Seminar, 1985. (Box 136, Folder 26)
  - Little Santa Christmas Party, ca. 1991. (Box 136, Folder 27)
  - Little Santa Christmas Party, not dated. (Box 136, Folder 28)
  - Little Santa Christmas Party, not dated. (Box 136, Folder 29)
  - Little Santa Christmas Party, not dated. (Box 136, Folder 30)
  - Charles Luger, not dated. (Box 136, Folder 31)
  - Robert Meakise, not dated. (Box 136, Folder 32)
  - Meeting, not dated. (Box 136, Folder 33)
  - Paul Mellor, not dated. (Box 136, Folder 34)
  - MGA and Political Debate, not dated. (Box 136, Folder 35)
  - Mid Year Chairman's Planning Guide Judging -- Fredericksburg, Virginia, 1990. (Box 136, Folder 36)
  - Lewis N. Miller, Jr., 1995. (Box 137, Folder 1)
  - T. Justin Moore, not dated. (Box 137, Folder 2)
  - Movie Night, not dated. (Box 137, Folder 3)
  - Party/Social, not dated. (Box 137, Folder 4)
  - Picnic, not dated. (Box 137, Folder 5)
  - Project W.A.R.M, 1990-1991. (Box 137, Folder 6)
  - Heath Rada, not dated. (Box 137, Folder 7)
  - Richmond illuminated, not dated. (Box 137, Folder 8)
  - Richmond Jaycees Christmas Party, not dated. (Box 137, Folder 9)
  - Richmond Jaycees 50th Anniversary Party, 1986. (Box 137, Folder 10)
  - Richmond Jaycees Members Photographs Unidentified, ca. 1980's. (Box 137, Folder 11)
  - Richmond Jaycess Members negatives, not dated. (Box 137, Folder 12)
  - Send Your Boss to Camp, not dated. (Box 137, Folder 13)
  - Skate-a-thon for Mentally,. (Box 137, Folder 14)
  - Jeff Smith -- President of Retail Merchants Association, ca. 1992. (Box 137, Folder 15)
  - Sonny Smith -- VCU Coach, ca. 1991. (Box 137, Folder 16)
  - Soap Box Derby, 1984. (Box 137, Folder 17)
  - Soap Box Derby, not dated. (Box 137, Folder 18)
  - Soap Box Derby, not dated. (Box 137, Folder 19)
  - Special Olympics, 1990. (Box 137, Folder 20)
  - Special Olympics, not dated. (Box 137, Folder 21)
  - Special Olympics, not dated. (Box 137, Folder 22)
  - Special Olympics, not dated. (Box 138, Folder 1)
  - Jeffrey B. Spence, not dated. (Box 138, Folder 2)
  - Sports Night negatives, ca. 1991. (Box 138, Folder 3)
  - Julie Spruell, not dated. (Box 138, Folder 4)
  - Summer Encore, 1990. (Box 138, Folder 5)
  - Summer Encore, not dated. (Box 138, Folder 6)
  - Summer Encore negatives, not dated. (Box 138, Folder 7)
  - Dick Tarrant -- Coach, University of Richmond, ca. 1991. (Box 138, Folder 8)
  - Unidentified Negatives, not dated. (Box 138, Folder 9)
  - Unidentified Negatives, not dated. (Box 138, Folder 10)
  - Unidentified Negatives, not dated. (Box 138, Folder 11)
  - Unidentified Negatives, not dated. (Box 138, Folder 12)
  - Unidentified Negatives, not dated. (Box 138, Folder 13)
  - Unidentified Negatives, not dated. (Box 138, Folder 14)
  - Unidentified Negatives, not dated. (Box 138, Folder 15)
  - Unidentified Negatives, not dated. (Box 138, Folder 16)
  - Unidentified Negatives, not dated. (Box 138, Folder 17)
  - Unidentified Negatives, not dated. (Box 138, Folder 18)
  - Unidentified Negatives, not dated. (Box 138, Folder 19)
  - Unidentified Negatives, not dated. (Box 138, Folder 20)
  - Unidentified Negatives, not dated. (Box 138, Folder 21)
  - Unidentified Negatives, not dated. (Box 138, Folder 22)
  - Unidentified Negatives, not dated. (Box 138, Folder 23)
  - Unidentified Photographs, ca. 1984. (Box 138, Folder 24)
  - Unidentified Photographs, ca. 1986. (Box 138, Folder 25)
  - Unidentified Photographs, 1986. (Box 138, Folder 26)
  - Unidentified Photographs, ca. 1987. (Box 138, Folder 27)
  - Unidentified Photographs, ca. 1987. (Box 138, Folder 28)
  - Unidentified Photographs, ca. 1990. (Box 138, Folder 29)
  - Unidentified Photographs, ca. 1990. (Box 138, Folder 30)
  - Unidentified Photographs, ca. 1990. (Box 138, Folder 31)
  - Unidentified Photographs, 1991. (Box 138, Folder 32)
  - Unidentified Photographs, 1991. (Box 138, Folder 33)
  - Unidentified Photographs, 1991. (Box 138, Folder 34)
  - Unidentified Photographs, ca. 1991. (Box 138, Folder 35)
  - Unidentified Photographs, ca. 1991. (Box 138, Folder 36)
  - Unidentified Photographs, ca. 1992. (Box 138, Folder 37)
  - Unidentified Photographs, ca. 1996. (Box 138, Folder 38)
  - Unidentified Photographs, not dated. (Box 138, Folder 39)
  - Unidentified Photographs, not dated. (Box 139, Folder 1)
  - Unidentified Photographs, not dated. (Box 139, Folder 2)
  - Unidentified Photographs, not dated. (Box 139, Folder 3)
  - Unidentified Photographs, not dated. (Box 139, Folder 4)
  - Unidentified Photographs, not dated. (Box 139, Folder 5)
  - Unidentified Photographs, not dated. (Box 139, Folder 6)
  - Unidentified Photographs, not dated. (Box 139, Folder 7)
  - Unidentified Photographs, not dated. (Box 139, Folder 8)
  - Unidentified Photographs, not dated. (Box 139, Folder 9)
  - Unidentified Photographs, not dated. (Box 139, Folder 10)
  - Unidentified Photographs, not dated. (Box 139, Folder 11)
  - Unidentified Photographs, not dated. (Box 139, Folder 12)
  - Unidentified Photographs, not dated. (Box 139, Folder 13)
  - Unidentified Photographs, not dated. (Box 139, Folder 14)
  - Unidentified Photographs, not dated. (Box 139, Folder 15)
  - Unidentified Photographs, not dated. (Box 139, Folder 16)
  - Unidentified Photographs, not dated. (Box 139, Folder 17)
  - Unidentified Photographs, ca. 1990. (Box 139, Folder 18)
  - Unidentified Photographs, not dated. (Box 139, Folder 19)
  - Unidentified Photographs, not dated. (Box 139, Folder 20)
  - Unidentified Photographs, not dated. (Box 140, Folder 1)
  - Unidentified Photographs, not dated. (Box 140, Folder 2)
  - Unidentified Photographs, not dated. (Box 140, Folder 3)
  - Unidentified Photographs, not dated. (Box 140, Folder 4)
  - Unidentified Photographs, not dated. (Box 140, Folder 5)
  - Unidentified Photographs, not dated. (Box 140, Folder 6)
  - Unidentified Photographs, not dated. (Box 140, Folder 7)
  - Unidentified Photographs, not dated. (Box 140, Folder 8)
  - Unidentified Photographs, not dated. (Box 140, Folder 9)
  - Unidentified Photographs, not dated. (Box 140, Folder 10)
  - Unidentified Photographs, not dated. (Box 140, Folder 11)
  - Unidentified Photographs, not dated. (Box 140, Folder 12)
  - Unidentified Photographs, not dated. (Box 140, Folder 13)
  - Unidentified Photographs, not dated. (Box 140, Folder 14)
  - Unidentified Photographs, not dated. (Box 140, Folder 15)
  - Unidentified Slides, not dated. (Box 140, Folder 16)
  - Volleyball, not dated. (Box 140, Folder 17)
  - Volleyball Tournament, ca. 1987. (Box 140, Folder 18)
  - Whacking Weeds for the Elderly, 1992. (Box 140, Folder 19)
  - Phil Whiteway receiving Richmond Outstanding Citizen Award, not dated. (Box 140, Folder 20)
  - Douglas Wilder, ca. 1990. (Box 140, Folder 21)
  - Wine Tasting, 1987. (Box 140, Folder 22)
  - Workshop, ca. 1975. (Box 140, Folder 23)
  - Yard Work for the Elderly, 1990. (Box 140, Folder 24)
  - Yard Work for the Elderly, not dated. (Box 140, Folder 25)
- Miscellaneous, 1964-1980.
  This series consists of two audio cassettes of speeches given at Richmond Jaycees meeting, a tee shirt from Camp Virginia Jaycees, and a banner from the 1964 Tokyo Olympic Games.
  - Dare to Care -- Camp Virginia Jaycee Tee Shirt, not dated. (Box 141)
  - Cassette Tape -- David H. Jaycee Speech, not dated. (Box 141)
  - Jaycees Campaign Speeches, 1980. (Box 141)
  - Tokoyo Olympic Games banner, 1964. (Box 141)